Viewers all over the world, thank you.
I know the thoughts of your heart; I mean, the disposition.
Yes.
I release healing - that organ of yours, I command it to be healed, in the name of Jesus!
Every infirmity, be healed, in the name of Jesus!
Satan, remove your hand from this man!
Remove your hand from this woman!
Remove your hand from my people!
You satan, I say, remove your hand from their business, career - remove your hand!
All knees shall bow at the name of Jesus.
I command you to remove your hand!
You satan, remove your hand from their career, business - remove your hand!
I can see you being released!
Everything that has been bound, be loosed!
Satan, I am waiting. Time to wait.
Pack your things, pack your load, your activities - I say, leave my people!
Leave my people, in Jesus Christ's name!